<faqlist:FAQList xmlns:faqlist="http://kp.org/tpmg/ttg/mdo/xml/faqlist">
<faqlist:FAQListTitle>Video Visits Support</faqlist:FAQListTitle>
<faqlist:FAQItems>
<faqlist:FAQItem>
<faqlist:Sequence>1</faqlist:Sequence>
<faqlist:FAQItemHeader>Learn About Video Visits</faqlist:FAQItemHeader>
<faqlist:ID>faq1</faqlist:ID>
<faqlist:Orientation>left</faqlist:Orientation>
<faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Title>What is a video visit?</faqlist:Title>
<faqlist:Section>faq1_1</faqlist:Section>
<faqlist:Url/>
<faqlist:Abstract>
<![CDATA[
Video visits are a way for you to meet with your doctor from the convenience of your home or office. You can securely connect with your doctor over the internet using your computer and webcam.
]]>
</faqlist:Abstract>
</faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Title>Where do I join my visit?</faqlist:Title>
<faqlist:Section>faq1_2</faqlist:Section>
<faqlist:Url/>
<faqlist:Abstract>
<![CDATA[
Join your visit at <a target="_blank" href="http://qa2.mydoctor.kaiserpermanente.org/videovisit">kp.org/mydoctor/videovisits</a>. If you received an appointment reminder by email, you can follow the link in that email as well.
 <br />
 <br />
 You'll be able to join your visit starting 15 minutes before the appointment time, but you can visit the website anytime to check your computer, webcam, speakers and microphone are ready.
 <br />
 <br />
 Please note: If you're joining the meeting as a guest of a Kaiser Permanente member, the <a href="#faq3_3">steps to join</a> are slightly different.
]]>
</faqlist:Abstract>
</faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Title>Can I join with a smartphone or tablet?</faqlist:Title>
<faqlist:Section>faq1_3</faqlist:Section>
<faqlist:Url/>
<faqlist:Abstract>
<![CDATA[
At this time, we recommend you join with a desktop or laptop computer. We hope to make it possible for you to join on your smartphone or tablet soon.
]]>
</faqlist:Abstract>
</faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Title>Are video visits private?</faqlist:Title>
<faqlist:Section>faq1_4</faqlist:Section>
<faqlist:Url/>
<faqlist:Abstract>
<![CDATA[
Yes! Video visits are secure and encrypted so only the participants of the visit can see and hear the meeting. Video visits are not recorded by Kaiser Permanente.
]]>
</faqlist:Abstract>
</faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Title>Do I have the right equipment for a visit?</faqlist:Title>
<faqlist:Section>faq1_5</faqlist:Section>
<faqlist:Url/>
<faqlist:Abstract>
<![CDATA[
<p>To join a video visit, you need a desktop or laptop computer with:</p>
 <ul>
 <li>a webcam and microphone (most webcams have a built-in microphone)
 <br /></li>
 <li>a strong and reliable internet connection</li>
 <li>a recent version of Adobe Flash.</li>
 </ul>
 <p>At this time, joining your visit with a mobile device (such as a smartphone or tablet) is not recommended.
 <br /></p>
 <p><br /></p>
 <p>A headset or headphones can improve the quality of the audio connection. Although it is not required, it is strongly recommended. Please join from a quiet, well-lit place so your doctor can see and hear you well.
 <br />
 <br />
 Before you appointment, visit <a target="_blank" href="http://qa2.mydoctor.kaiserpermanente.org/videovisit">kp.org/mydoctor/videovisits</a> to check that your computer's webcam, speakers and microphone are ready to use.</p>
]]>
</faqlist:Abstract>
</faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Title>How do I prepare for a visit?</faqlist:Title>
<faqlist:Section>faq1_6</faqlist:Section>
<faqlist:Url/>
<faqlist:Abstract>
<![CDATA[
Before your appointment, visit <a target="_blank" href="http://qa2.mydoctor.kaiserpermanente.org/videovisit">kp.org/mydoctor/videovisits</a> to check that your computer's webcam, speakers and microphone are ready to use. Please join from a quiet, well-lit place so your doctor can see and hear you well. If this is your first video visit, plan to join 5 to 10 minutes in advance to make sure everything goes smoothly.
]]>
</faqlist:Abstract>
</faqlist:Hyperlink>
</faqlist:FAQItem>
<faqlist:FAQItem>
<faqlist:Sequence>2</faqlist:Sequence>
<faqlist:FAQItemHeader>Scheduling a Video Visit</faqlist:FAQItemHeader>
<faqlist:ID>faq2</faqlist:ID>
<faqlist:Orientation>left</faqlist:Orientation>
<faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Title>How do I schedule a video visit</faqlist:Title>
<faqlist:Section>faq2_1</faqlist:Section>
<faqlist:Url/>
<faqlist:Abstract>
<![CDATA[
You may be offered the choice to meet with your doctor by video. When scheduling an appointment, ask if a video visit is available.
]]>
</faqlist:Abstract>
</faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Title>How do I cancel or reschedule a video visit?</faqlist:Title>
<faqlist:Section>faq2_2</faqlist:Section>
<faqlist:Url/>
<faqlist:Abstract>
<![CDATA[
<p>There are a few ways to cancel or reschedule an existing video appointment.
 <br /></p>
 <p><br /></p>
 <ul>
 <li>You may have received an email reminder with information about cancelling and rescheduling your visit.</li>
 <li>You may manage your appointments through the Appointment Center on kp.org. If you don’t have an active kp.org account, you can activate a new account quickly and easily.</li>
 <li>View and manage your appointments on our KP Preventive Care mobile app.</li>
 <li>If your appointment is with a doctor in Adult Medicine, Pediatrics, Women’s Health or Optometry, you can cancel by calling 1-888-454-8855.</li>
 </ul>
]]>
</faqlist:Abstract>
</faqlist:Hyperlink>
</faqlist:FAQItem>
<faqlist:FAQItem>
<faqlist:Sequence>3</faqlist:Sequence>
<faqlist:FAQItemHeader>Joining a Video Visit</faqlist:FAQItemHeader>
<faqlist:ID>faq3</faqlist:ID>
<faqlist:Orientation>left</faqlist:Orientation>
<faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Title>How do I join a video visit?</faqlist:Title>
<faqlist:Section>faq3_1</faqlist:Section>
<faqlist:Url/>
<faqlist:Abstract>
<![CDATA[
<p>Join your visit at <a target="_blank" href="http://qa2.mydoctor.kaiserpermanente.org/videovisit">kp.org/mydoctor/videovisits</a>. If you received an appointment reminder by email, you can follow the link in that email as well. To protect your personal health information, you'll be asked to enter your last name, medical record number, and date of birth during the sign on process. </p>
 <p><br /></p>
 <p>You'll be able to view and join your visit starting 15 minutes before the appointment time, but you can visit the website anytime to check your computer, webcam, speakers and microphone are ready.</p>
]]>
</faqlist:Abstract>
</faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Title>I'm having trouble signing on.</faqlist:Title>
<faqlist:Section>faq3_2</faqlist:Section>
<faqlist:Url/>
<faqlist:Abstract>
<![CDATA[
<p>For security purposes, you'll be asked to enter your last name, medical record number and date of birth during the sign on process. </p>
 <ul>
 <li>Make sure you spell your last name correctly and that you enter your birth date in the correct format.</li>
 <li>If this appointment is for your child (or other member of your family), be sure you’re entering his or her MRN, date of birth, and last name and not your own.</li>
 <li>Your medical record number is listed on your Kaiser Permanente ID card. If you don’t know what your medical record is, call member services at 1-800-464-4000.
 <br /></li>
 </ul>
 <p>If you're joining the meeting as a guest of a Kaiser Permanente member, the steps to join are slightly different.</p>
]]>
</faqlist:Abstract>
</faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Title>
I've been invited as the guest of a Kaiser Permanente member. How do I join?
</faqlist:Title>
<faqlist:Section>faq3_3</faqlist:Section>
<faqlist:Url/>
<faqlist:Abstract>
<![CDATA[
If you're joining the meeting as a guest of a Kaiser Permanente member, you will receive an invitation by e-mail. When it's time to join your meeting, follow the link in that –e-mail reminder. You'll be asked to enter the patient's last name (not your own), and then you can join the visit.
 <br />
 <br />
 The link you receive in your e-mail reminder is specific to the visit you're joining and will work only once. This means that if you're joining more than one meeting as a patient guest, it's important to follow the link from the correct e-mail each time. While patients can join from the main video visits website, patient guests must always follow the link they receive by e-mail.
]]>
</faqlist:Abstract>
</faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Title>What is my medical record number?</faqlist:Title>
<faqlist:Section>faq3_4</faqlist:Section>
<faqlist:Url/>
<faqlist:Abstract>
<![CDATA[
Your medical record number is listed on your Kaiser Permanente ID card. If you don’t know what your medical record is, call member services at 1-800-464-4000.
]]>
</faqlist:Abstract>
</faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Title>I see an error message.</faqlist:Title>
<faqlist:Section>faq3_5</faqlist:Section>
<faqlist:Url/>
<faqlist:Abstract>
<![CDATA[
<p>
 <strong>Adobe Flash:</strong> If you see an error message stating that you do not have Adobe Flash installed, please go to the Adobe website and download and install the latest version of Adobe Flash.</p>
 <p><strong>Blocked cookies:</strong> If you use Apple's Safari browser, you may see an error messaging saying you need to unblock cookies. There's a setting you'll need to change before joining your visit:</p>
 <ul>
 <li>Go to the "Preference" menu within the Safari browser.</li>
 <li>Go to the "Privacy" tab and choose "Never" next to the "Block cookies" option.</li>
 <li>Close your browser and try again.
 <br />
 <img src="http://qa1stg.mydoctor.kaiserpermanente.org/ncal/Images/blocked%20cookies.png" style="width: 673px; height: 310px;" alt="blocked_cookies" title="blocked_cookies" /></li>
 </ul>
]]>
</faqlist:Abstract>
</faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Title>I need to unblock cookies.</faqlist:Title>
<faqlist:Section>faq3_6</faqlist:Section>
<faqlist:Url/>
<faqlist:Abstract>
<![CDATA[
<div>Blocked cookies: If you use Apple's Safari browser, you may see an error messaging saying you need to unblock cookies. There's a setting you'll need to change before joining your visit:
 <ul>
 <li>Go to the "Preferences" menu within the Safari browser. </li>
 <li>Go to the "Privacy" tab and choose "Never" next to the "Block cookies" option.</li>
 <li>Close your browser and try again.
 
 </li>
 </ul>
 </div>
]]>
</faqlist:Abstract>
</faqlist:Hyperlink>
</faqlist:FAQItem>
<faqlist:FAQItem>
<faqlist:Sequence>4</faqlist:Sequence>
<faqlist:FAQItemHeader>Video Troubleshooting</faqlist:FAQItemHeader>
<faqlist:ID>faq4</faqlist:ID>
<faqlist:Orientation>right</faqlist:Orientation>
<faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Title>My video is slow or choppy.</faqlist:Title>
<faqlist:Section>faq4_1</faqlist:Section>
<faqlist:Url/>
<faqlist:Abstract>
<![CDATA[ Text pending ]]>
</faqlist:Abstract>
</faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Title>I can't see my doctor.</faqlist:Title>
<faqlist:Section>faq4_2</faqlist:Section>
<faqlist:Url/>
<faqlist:Abstract>
<![CDATA[
<p>If you're able to talk to your doctor, let her know that you can't see her. She may need to active or adjust her webcam or computer settings.
 <br />
 <br />
 If the image you see is poor quality:</p>
 <ul>
 <li>Ask your doctor to adjust the lighting in her office</li>
 <li>Ask your doctor to come closer to the screen</li>
 <li>You can manually increase the size of your doctor's image by clicking and dragging the lower-right corner of her video feed. </li>
 </ul>
 Some visual problems can be caused by a slow internet connection, either on your computer or your doctors. <a href="https://qa2.mydoctor.kaiserpermanente.org:2443/videovisit/mdohelp.htm#faq2_2">Read more</a>
]]>
</faqlist:Abstract>
</faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Title>My doctor can't see me.</faqlist:Title>
<faqlist:Section>faq4_3</faqlist:Section>
<faqlist:Url/>
<faqlist:Abstract>
<![CDATA[
If your image does not appear for your doctor, first check that your webcam is on and working properly. Leave the video visit (let your doctor know that you'll be back in a minute) and troubleshoot using our <span style="text-decoration: underline;">set-up wizard</span> and <a href="https://qa2.mydoctor.kaiserpermanente.org:2443/videovisit/mdohelp.htm#faq6_4">webcam tips</a>.
 <br />
 <img src="http://qa1stg.mydoctor.kaiserpermanente.org/ncal/Images/check%20your%20video.png" style="width: 476px; height: 141px;" alt="check_your_video" title="check_your_video" />
 <br />
 If your doctor can see you but says the image quality is poor:
 <br />
 <ul>
 <li>Try adjusting the lighting in the room. Try to avoid being backlit by a lamp or window. The best position for the camera is between you and your light source.
 <br /></li>
 <li>Sit closer to the screen if your doctor says your image is small.</li>
 </ul>
 <p>Some visual problems can be caused by a slow internet connection, either on your computer or your doctor’s computer.</p>
]]>
</faqlist:Abstract>
</faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Title>My webcam isn't working.</faqlist:Title>
<faqlist:Section>faq4_4</faqlist:Section>
<faqlist:Url/>
<faqlist:Abstract>
<![CDATA[
<p>
 <strong>Check that your webcam is plugged in:</strong> If you're using an external webcam that plugs into your USB drive (instead of a webcam that's built into your computer), check to make sure it's securely plugged in to your USB port. After you connect it, close and re-op
]]>
<![CDATA[
en your internet browser window.</p>
 <ul>
 <li><strong>Check that your webcam is turned on:</strong>  Most webcams turn on automatically, but If your webcam has an external power switch make sure it's turned on.</li>
 <li><strong>Multiple webcams:</strong> If you have more than one webcam, select the webcam you'd like to use for video visit. Open the set-up wizard &lt;link pending&gt;, and select a camera from the "check your video" section, as shown below:
 <br />
 <img src="http://qa1stg.mydoctor.kaiserpermanente.org/ncal/Images/check%20your%20video%20-%20choose%20camera.png" style="width: 467px; height: 142px;" alt="check_your_video-choose_camera" title="check_your_video-choose_camera" />
 <br />
 A list of your webcams will appear. Select the camera you'd like to use for the video visit. If you don't see the "choose camera" option, our application is only detecting a single webcam.</li>
 <li><strong>Close other applications:</strong> Make sure that no other application is using your webcam. Please close any other open application that is using your webcam (e.g., Skype, Google Hangout, or any other application that may have come with your webcam).  </li>
 <li><strong>Allow access</strong>: If you accidentally clicked "Deny" when prompted to allow Video Visits to use your webcam, click the "Refresh" button on your web browser and join the visit again. You should be prompted to allow or deny access to your webcam: click "Allow."
 <br />
 <img src="http://qa1stg.mydoctor.kaiserpermanente.org/ncal/Images/adobe%20flash%20player%20settings.png" style="width: 225px; height: 144px;" alt="adobe_flash_player_settings" title="adobe_flash_player_settings" />
 <br /></li>
 <li><strong>Refresh your browser:</strong> If you have already joined a video visit and plugged in your webcam afterwards, try to refresh your browser window or close and re-open your web browser.</li>
 <li><strong>Check your internet connection:</strong> Some visual problems can be caused by a slow connection.</li>
 </ul>
]]>
</faqlist:Abstract>
</faqlist:Hyperlink>
</faqlist:FAQItem>
<faqlist:FAQItem>
<faqlist:Sequence>5</faqlist:Sequence>
<faqlist:FAQItemHeader>Audio Troubleshooting</faqlist:FAQItemHeader>
<faqlist:ID>faq5</faqlist:ID>
<faqlist:Orientation>right</faqlist:Orientation>
<faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Title>I can't hear my doctor.</faqlist:Title>
<faqlist:Section>faq5_1</faqlist:Section>
<faqlist:Url/>
<faqlist:Abstract>
<![CDATA[
<p>If you're able to hear some of what your doctor is saying, let her know that you can't hear clearly. She may need to increase the volume of her microphone, speak louder or more clearly, or minimize any background noise that's preventing you from hearing her. If she has a headset she can use, this may help you hear more clearly.</p>
 <p><br /></p>
 <p>Test and adjust your speakers, or use a headset:</p>
 <ul>
 <li><strong>Test your speakers:</strong> Check that your speakers are turned on and unmuted and the volume is up. Our <span style="text-decoration: underline;">set-up wizard</span> can help you check this.
 <br />
 <img src="http://qa1stg.mydoctor.kaiserpermanente.org/ncal/Images/test%20your%20speakers.png" style="width: 464px; height: 89px;" alt="test_your_speakers" title="test_your_speakers" />
 <br /></li>
 <li><strong>Unmute and adjust speaker volume.</strong> Adjust your speaker volume and make sure your speakers are not on mute.</li>
 <li><strong>Try a headset:</strong> A headset or headphones can improve the quality of the audio connection. If you have headphones you use for your smartphone or mp3 player, see if they allow you to hear well. They'll work with or without a built-in microphone.</li>
 <li><strong>Check your internet connection:</strong> Some audio problems can be caused by a slow connection.</li>
 <li><strong>Switch to a phone:</strong>  If you and your doctor are not able to hear each other, you can connect by phone. Mute your microphone and speakers so they do not interfere with your phone call.
 </li>
 </ul>
]]>
</faqlist:Abstract>
</faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Title>My doctor can't hear me.</faqlist:Title>
<faqlist:Section>faq5_2</faqlist:Section>
<faqlist:Url/>
<faqlist:Abstract>
<![CDATA[
<ul>
 <li><strong>Test your microphone</strong>: Check that your microphone is turned on and the volume is up. Our <span style="text-decoration: underline;">set-up wizard</span> can help you check this.
 <br />
 <img src="http://qa1stg.mydoctor.kaiserpermanente.org/ncal/Images/test%20your%20mic.png" style="width: 477px; height: 90px;" alt="test_your_mic" title="test_your_mic" />
 <br /></li>
 <li><strong>Unmute or adjust microphone volume:</strong> To help your doctor hear you, you may need unmute or adjust your microphone volume.</li>
 <li><strong>Check your microphone is plugged in:</strong> If you're using an external microphone (instead of the one that's built-in to your computer), make sure it's plugged in securely.</li>
 <li><strong>Check your microphone is turned on:</strong>  Most microphones turn on automatically, but if yours has a switch on the side make sure it's turned on.</li>
 <li><strong>Multiple microphones:</strong> If you have more than one microphone, select the one you'd like to use for video visit. Open the <span style="text-decoration: underline;">set-up wizard</span>, and select choose mic from the "Test your mic" section, as shown below:
 <br />
 <img src="http://qa1stg.mydoctor.kaiserpermanente.org/ncal/Images/test%20your%20mic%20-%20choose%20mic.png" style="width: 478px; height: 89px;" alt="test_your_mic-choose_mic" title="test_your_mic-choose_mic" />
 <br />
 <br />
 A list of your microphones will appear. Select the mic you'd like to use for the video visit. If you don't see the "choose mic" option, our application is only detecting a single microphone</li>
 <li><strong>Minimize background noise:</strong> Make sure you're joining your visit from a quiet place.</li>
 <li><strong>Try a headset:</strong> A headset or headphones can improve the quality of the audio connection. If you have headphones you use for your smartphone or mp3 player, see if they allow you to hear well.</li>
 <li><strong>Check your internet connection:</strong> Some audio problems can be caused by a slow connection.</li>
 <li><strong>Switch to a phone:</strong>  If you and your doctor are not able to hear each other, you can connect by phone.</li>
 </ul>
]]>
</faqlist:Abstract>
</faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Title>What kind of headsets can I use?</faqlist:Title>
<faqlist:Section>faq5_3</faqlist:Section>
<faqlist:Url/>
<faqlist:Abstract>
<![CDATA[
<p>Many types of headsets or headphones will work for Video Visits. Headsets designed for internet audio connection work well, as will earbuds (the kind you use for a smartphone or mp3 player). Headphones will work with or without a built-in microphone.</p>
 <p><br /></p>
 <p>If you have a headset or headphones that you want to check, launch our setup wizard:</p>
 <ul>
 <li>see if you can hear clearly</li>
 <li>(if your headphones/headset has a built in microphone) make sure your microphone is working correctly.
 </li>
 </ul>
]]>
</faqlist:Abstract>
</faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Title>I need to unmute or adjust my microphone volume.</faqlist:Title>
<faqlist:Section>faq5_4</faqlist:Section>
<faqlist:Url/>
<faqlist:Abstract>
<![CDATA[
<ul>
 <li><strong>Unmute microphone:</strong> You can mute and unmute you microphone from within the video visits environment. Click on the green microphone button located in the control panel on the right side of the video visit screen, underneath your own video feed. This button toggles your microphone on/off.  
 <br />
 On:
 <br />
     <img src="http://qa1stg.mydoctor.kaiserpermanente.org/ncal/Images/audio%20status%20ON.png" style="width: 180px; height: 118px;" alt="audio_status_ON" title="audio_status_ON" /></li>
 </ul>
 <p>          Off:</p>
 <p>              <img src="http://qa1stg.mydoctor.kaiserpermanente.org/ncal/Images/audio%20status%20OFF.png" style="width: 183px; height: 121px;" alt="audio_status_OFF" title="audio_status_OFF" /></p>
 <p>         You know that your microphone is being used if the microphone button is green, and the horizontal loudness meter underneath moves while you speak.</p>
 <ul>
 <li><strong>Adjust microphone volume:</strong> To increase the sensitivity of your microphone, slide the vertical slider located to the left of the microphone button – sliding it up increases sensitivity. Please note that increasing it too much may cause feedback or other audio artifacts, so move it in small increments at first.
 <br />
 <img src="http://qa1stg.mydoctor.kaiserpermanente.org/ncal/Images/adjust%20microphone%20volume.png" style="width: 239px; height: 120px;" alt="adjust_microphone_volume" title="adjust_microphone_volume" />    </li>
 </ul>
]]>
</faqlist:Abstract>
</faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Title>I need to unmute or adjust my speaker volume.</faqlist:Title>
<faqlist:Section>faq5_5</faqlist:Section>
<faqlist:Url/>
<faqlist:Abstract>
<![CDATA[
<p>For Windows users: In the lower-right portion of your computer screen look for a small speaker icon. Click it once and a volume adjuster will display. Make sure that "Mute" is unchecked and that the volume is at an adequate level.  </p>
 <p>    <img src="http://qa1stg.mydoctor.kaiserpermanente.org/ncal/Images/volume.jpg" style="width: 141px; height: 38px;" alt="volume" title="volume" />
 <br /></p>
 <p>For Mac users: Unmute and adjust the volume of your speakers using the volume buttons on the right-side of the top row of your Mac keyboard.</p>
 <p>    <img src="http://qa1stg.mydoctor.kaiserpermanente.org/ncal/Images/adjusting_volume.jpg" style="width: 146px; height: 188px;" alt="adjusting_volume" title="adjusting_volume" />
 </p>
]]>
</faqlist:Abstract>
</faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Title>I hear an echo or delays in audio.</faqlist:Title>
<faqlist:Section>faq5_6</faqlist:Section>
<faqlist:Url/>
<faqlist:Abstract>
<![CDATA[
<ul>
 <li>Try a headset: A headset or headphones can improve the quality of the audio connection. If you have headphones you use for your smartphone or mp3 player, see if they allow you to hear well. They'll work with or without a built-in microphone.</li>
 <li>Check your internet connection: Some audio problems can be caused by a slow connection.
 </li>
 </ul>
]]>
</faqlist:Abstract>
</faqlist:Hyperlink>
</faqlist:FAQItem>
<faqlist:FAQItem>
<faqlist:Sequence>6</faqlist:Sequence>
<faqlist:FAQItemHeader>Connection Problems</faqlist:FAQItemHeader>
<faqlist:ID>faq6</faqlist:ID>
<faqlist:Orientation>right</faqlist:Orientation>
<faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Title>Why a good internet connection is important</faqlist:Title>
<faqlist:Section>faq6_1</faqlist:Section>
<faqlist:Url/>
<faqlist:Abstract>
<![CDATA[
A slow internet connection can cause problems with video and audio. To prevent low quality images that freeze or move slowly or delayed, choppy audio, please join your video visit meeting with the strongest connection possible.
]]>
</faqlist:Abstract>
</faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Title>How do I determine my connection speed?</faqlist:Title>
<faqlist:Section>faq6_2</faqlist:Section>
<faqlist:Url/>
<faqlist:Abstract>
<![CDATA[
<p>Check that your internet connection is strong enough to support a successful video visit. Our set-up wizard can help you check this.</p>
 <p><img src="http://qa1stg.mydoctor.kaiserpermanente.org/ncal/Images/video%20visit%20preparation.png" style="width: 590px; height: 125px;" alt="video_visit_preparation" title="video_visit_preparation" />
 </p>
]]>
</faqlist:Abstract>
</faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Hyperlink>
<faqlist:Title>How can I improve my connection?</faqlist:Title>
<faqlist:Section>faq6_3</faqlist:Section>
<faqlist:Url/>
<faqlist:Abstract>
<![CDATA[
<ul>
 <li><strong>Connect by wire:</strong> A wired internet connection is stronger and more reliable than a wireless one. If you are able, connect to your wireless router with a &lt;&gt; cord.</li>
 <li><strong>Move closer to your router:</strong> If you're using wireless, move closer to your wireless router.</li>
 <li><strong>Close other applications:</strong> Close extra applications running on your computer and any open browser windows not being used by Video Visits.</li>
 <li><strong>Limit access to your wireless network:</strong> If you share your wireless connection with others, limiting their access may increase the quality of your connection.</li>
 </ul>
]]>
</faqlist:Abstract>
</faqlist:Hyperlink>
</faqlist:FAQItem>
</faqlist:FAQItems>
</faqlist:FAQList>